A Inventory of the Pictorial Miscellany Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
Pictorial Miscellany Collection
circa 1900-1991
XX773
1 manuscript box, 14 envelopes (0.8 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Photographs depicting miscellaneous or unidentified scenes. Includes photographs of various United Nations officials and activities, and of atomic weapons testing.
Administrative Information
Access
The collection is open for research
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in Stanford University's online catalog.
Subjects
United Nations--Pictorial works.; Nuclear weapons--Testing--Pictorial works.; Latin America--Pictorial works.
Container List
- 2 prints depicting American Relief Administration activities in Russia; 3 prints of an unidentified U.S. (?) cemetery, with a monument; 1 print of Nancy A. Dyar and 1 print of Nessa L. Wilk, both supervisors of Teacher Education, U.C., Berkeley. (File A)
- 1 print of Elliot V. Fry; 2 prints of Japanese officers, one being Tomosaburo Kato, 1915. (File B)
- 1 print depicting an African art work; 1 print of a North Vietnamese (?) military cemetery, 1960's; 1 studio portrait of an unidentified officer taken in Washington, D.C. (File m*C)
- 6 glass mounted transparencies depicting scenes of World War II (?) (Box 1)
- 14 prints depicting atomic weapon testing. (File mD)
- 6 prints of Montefiore and 1 print of Kadlunga Station, in Australia. (File mE)
- 1 print of Mazatlan, Mexico; 1 print of Guatemala City, 1 print of the Panama Canal. (File F)
- 1 print of Dag Hammarskjold, which was used for commencement publicity at Stanford, 1955. (File G)
- 1 print depicting Special Services Officers dining with violinist Yehudi Menuhin, somewhere in England. (File H)
- 1 print of Cyrus H. Street, editor and publisher of The United Nations in Berkeley, California, 1908-1911. (File I)
- 1 print of depicting scenes of the founding ceremonies of the United Nations in San Francisco, 1945. (File J)
  35mm contact prints, all in one.
- 96 prints depicting United Nations officials and activities, 1950-1953. (File K-L)
- Five color prints of Chilean war murals during 1989 election; 6 prints of a Communist youth construction brigade; 2 prints of mass meetings in Chile, ca. early 1970s; and 7 color prints of the Sons of Gwalia mine, Australia, 1991. (File M)
- 1 print of unidentified man, n.d.; 1 print of a daughter of Manuel Noriega, n.d.; 1 print of an unidentified ship (File mN)
- 3 prints of a Spanish Republican delegation in Mexico, 1936. (File O)